coffeeshopr.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy

We collect information from you (such as name and e-mail address) when you subscribe to our free e-mail newsletter or registering on our website to comment on our blog posts.

We use Google Analytics to analyze our visitor traffic in order to improve our website, and as part of that your IP address and time of visit may be recorded. You may, however, visit our site anonymously through a VPN, or by disabling javascript in your browser or using a plugin that blocks trackers.

## **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used to send our periodic free e-mail newsletter. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter or submit your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server.

## **Do we use cookies?**

We use third party services for analytical purposes, and in some cases those services may use cookies.

## **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## **Children Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We do not aim to collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website is directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## **Terms of  Use**

Please also visit our Terms of Use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website [here](http://coffeeshopr.com/terms-use/ "Terms of Use").

## **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

## **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on February 26, 2014.

## **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us [here](http://coffeeshopr.com/contact-page/ "Say Hello").
